// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Formal groups are used to ",
        answer: "organize and distribute work",
        options: [
            "organize and distribute work",
            "work independently",
            "make things more clearly",
            "feel like family "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Team characteristics should include one of following factors ",
        answer: "Interaction",
        options: [
            "Interaction",
            "Short-term relation ",
            "Act independently ",
            "Unreacted members "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 3,
        question: "When do you need to work alone?  ",
        answer: "Minimum discretion is required ",
        options: [
            "Highly complex tasks or problems ",
            "Minimum discretion is required ",
            "High level of choice and uncertainty ",
            "Decisions by consensus are essential "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How many people does “a span of control” structure averagely have in their team?  ",
        answer: "5",
        options: [
            "3",
            "5",
            "7",
            "10"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Who do staffs report to in a matrix team?  ",
        answer: "Different managers",
        options: [
            "Single manager ",
            "Different managers",
            "General manager",
            "CEO of the organization"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 6,
        question: "A team is called contract team if",
        answer: "Team retains their responsibility for both their daily work and project work",
        options: [
            "Team members have other duties to perform in their normal functional units",
            "Team retains their responsibility for both their daily work and project work",
            "Team members report to different managers",
            "Team is brought in from outside in order to do project work"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is Social Value Orientation (SVO)?  ",
        answer: "People’s preferences when dividing resources between themselves and others",
        options: [
            "People prefer to organize and distribute work between themselves",
            "People’s preferences when dividing resources between themselves and others",
            "People dislike others’ work and try to prove their outcome is much better",
            "People are not cooperative and tend to work alone"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Andrew is a good listener and he always tries to understand what people think and why people feel in their own way. Andrew has ability of  ",
        answer: "empathy",
        options: [
            "empathy",
            "considerable skills",
            "caring ",
            "interdependence"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which one is the key component in cooperation?  ",
        answer: "Trust ",
        options: [
            "Honesty",
            "Hard working ",
            "Generosity  ",
            "Trust "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is one of disadvantages having large group?  ",
        answer: "Reduce communication ",
        options: [
            "Overestimate their abilities",
            "Rank themselves above average ",
            "More involvement",
            "Reduce communication "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Janet does not want to get involved in any disputes, discussion or conversations with her colleagues. She gets to work late and fails to show up at meetings as she wants to avoid any tasks may be assigned to her. However, she always wants to be apart of any success her team made. Economists call this kind of person is:   ",
        answer: "Free rider problem",
        options: [
            "Pretending",
            "Untrustworthy",
            "Dishonest ",
            "Free rider problem"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 12,
        question: "The need for self-evaluation experiment has shown that people come to know about themselves by ",
        answer: "comparing with others",
        options: [
            "having positive attitude in life ",
            "comparing with others",
            "seeking happiness",
            "feeling complete  "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Some people consider social norms and the opinions of others to help justify their own positions in life, some others consider _____ to perform better.    ",
        answer: "performance and abilities ",
        options: [
            "opinions and values",
            "performance and abilities ",
            "opinions and values  ",
            "similarity and friendliness"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 14,
        question: "What are the two main factors in social comparison?  ",
        answer: "Relevance and similarity",
        options: [
            "Similarity and friendliness ",
            "Openness and independence   ",
            "Relevance and similarity",
            "Self-esteem and trustworthy   "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 15,
        question: "When people can boost their own self-evaluations by comparing themselves to others ranked lower in a company, they are having  ",
        answer: "self-enhanced effect  ",
        options: [
            "life side effect",
            "bad behavior",
            "self-enhanced effect  ",
            "self-evaluation maintenance "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 16,
        question: "What are the positive effects of upward comparison? ",
        answer: "Hope and inspiration",
        options: [
            "Hope and inspiration",
            "Happy and gratitude   ",
            "Gratitude and scorn  ",
            "Dissatisfaction "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 17,
        question: "What is the negative effect of downward comparison? ",
        answer: "Scorn  ",
        options: [
            "Envy",
            "Dissatisfaction",
            "Scorn  ",
            "Pessimistic"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 18,
        question: "Social comparison can lead to  ",
        answer: "impacts on self-esteem, feeling of envy, feeling of regret  ",
        options: [
            "impacts on self-esteem, feeling of victory, feeling of humbleness   ",
            "impacts on self-esteem, feeling of envy, feeling of regret  ",
            "impacts on self-esteem, feeling of love, feeling of being superior  ",
            "Impacts on self-satisfaction, self-esteem, feeling of loser"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 19,
        question: "The SEM model suggests that managers may prefer sub optimal candidates because these candidates are not likely to  ",
        answer: "threaten the managers’ position   ",
        options: [
            "be more competitive  ",
            "seek for opinions",
            "compare themselves to others",
            "threaten the managers’ position   "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 20,
        question: "What is groupthink?  ",
        answer: "Group members are incapable of making a rational decision",
        options: [
            "Group members are incapable of making a rational decision",
            "Group members share same thought in a specific topic",
            "Group members want to be alike in everything",
            "Group members decide to support each other"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 21,
        question: "People who consider upward comparison as a threat, have ",
        answer: "fixed mindset",
        options: [
            "negative mindset",
            "growth mindset",
            "fixed mindset",
            "jealous feelings"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 22,
        question: "When the number of comparison targets increase, social comparison tends to",
        answer: "decrease ",
        options: [
            "increase   ",
            "remain the same ",
            "be distorted  ",
            "decrease "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 23,
        question: "People usually compare with friends or co-workers than they are to industry or national averages, what is this comparison called in situational factors? ",
        answer: "Local   ",
        options: [
            "Number",
            "Local   ",
            "Proximity to a standard ",
            "Self-relevant  "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 24,
        question: "One of the key findings in the Dunning-Kruger effect experiments is  unskilled people are  ",
        answer: "overconfident with results   ",
        options: [
            "always satisfied with results",
            "often jealous with others",
            "unrewarded and biased ",
            "overconfident with results   "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 25,
        question: "One of the key findings in the Dunning-Kruger effect experiments is top performers tend to ",
        answer: "underestimate their skills ",
        options: [
            "overestimate their skills ",
            "rank themselves above average ",
            "underestimate their skills ",
            "always satisfied with results"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 26,
        question: "In group decision making process, if there are more people agree on certain point of view, we may consider the fact that the group has",
        answer: "group polarization ",
        options: [
            "complete agreement ",
            "group polarization ",
            "group sharing knowledge ",
            "All resources are mobilized "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 27,
        question: "People can claim that they can live independently and separately but they actually have  ",
        answer: "a need to belong",
        options: [
            "a need to belong",
            "a need to be included ",
            "a need to talk to someone",
            "None of these correct"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 28,
        question: "Groups not only satisfy need to belong, but also provide information, assistance and  ",
        answer: "social support ",
        options: [
            "developed Skills  ",
            "better Communication  ",
            "social support ",
            "motivation"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 29,
        question: "The psychological significance of groups include the need to belong, identity and membership, evolutionary advantages of group living and   ",
        answer: "affiliation in groups  ",
        options: [
            "respect in groups",
            "affiliation in groups  ",
            "trust in groups  ",
            "interdependence in groups  "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 30,
        question: "What is the main advantage of social facilitation?  ",
        answer: "Perform tasks improved ",
        options: [
            "Feel better ",
            "Perform tasks improved ",
            "Work more independently ",
            "Have high chance of promotion"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 31,
        question: "Which situation below is considered social loafing?  ",
        answer: "A student does all the group homework ",
        options: [
            "A single student works alone on a paper  ",
            "A student does all the group homework ",
            "Three students work on homework together ",
            "The whole group equally work hard on group assignment"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 32,
        question: "Four group level factors that combine to cause groupthink are  ",
        answer: "cohesion, isolation, biased leadership, decisional stress ",
        options: [
            "cohesion, isolation, biased leadership, decisional stress ",
            "cohesion, isolation, discouragement, biased leadership",
            "cohesion, isolation, decisional stress, aggressiveness ",
            "isolation, biased leadership, aggressiveness, discouragement"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 33,
        question: "Why is making group decision better than making individual decision? ",
        answer: "More objective evaluation",
        options: [
            "More objective evaluation",
            "Team members feel encouraged to do so",
            "No one left behind the process ",
            "Group decision is inferior to an individual decision"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 34,
        question: "You start planning a proposal by",
        answer: "stating the problem.",
        options: [
            "determining the factors.",
            "determining the solutions.",
            "scheduling the study.",
            "stating the problem."
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 35,
        question: "The most important section of a proposal is the",
        answer: "solution ",
        options: [
            "cost",
            "solution ",
            "purpose statement",
            "background "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 36,
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a strategy to avoid the occurrence of Groupthink?",
        answer: "Having a charismatic leader of the group",
        options: [
            "Appointing devils' advocates in discussions",
            "Using outside experts",
            "Having a charismatic leader of the group",
            "Allocating different groups for different tasks"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 37,
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a negative outcomes of Groupthink occurring?",
        answer: "Needing to seek outside expertise",
        options: [
            "Not examining alternatives",
            "No contingency plans",
            "Not seeking expert opinion",
            "Needing to seek outside expertise"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 38,
        question: "Which age group is often characterized by the tendency to rethink decisions and lean toward more permanent choices?",
        answer: "27–31",
        options: [
            "12-17",
            "18–26",
            "27–31",
            "32–42"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 39,
        question: "What kind of students has been shown by research to stay in college longer, be more goal focused and motivated, and have a more satisfying and fulfilling college experience?",
        answer: "Students who get involved in career-planning activities early",
        options: [
            "Students who have good social relationships",
            "Students who have excellent leadership skills",
            "Students who show great passion for the subjects they are studying",
            "Students who get involved in career-planning activities early"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 40,
        question: "One of the three categories of social value orientation (SVO) is?  ",
        answer: "Cooperative ",
        options: [
            "Incompetent",
            "Cooperative ",
            "Obsessive  ",
            "Generous  "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 41,
        question: "Strategy (ies) to develop yourself as a critical thinker",
        answer: "All are correct",
        options: [
            "Redefine the way you see things",
            "Reflect and practice",
            "Express yourself",
            "All are correct"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 42,
        question: "What is thinking?",
        answer: "Is the mental process you use to form associations and models of the world",
        options: [
            "Is the mental process you use to form associations and models of the world",
            "Is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it",
            "Is the act of thinking that produces thoughts, which arise as ideas, images, sounds, or even emotions",
            "All of these are correct"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 43,
        question: "What is pattern of thought?",
        answer: "Is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it",
        options: [
            "Is the mental process you use to form associations and models of the world",
            "Is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it",
            "Is the act of thinking that produces thoughts, which arise as ideas, images, sounds, or even emotions",
            "Is the manipulation of information to form concepts, to engage in problem-solving, to reason, and to make decisions"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 44,
        question: "Learning objectives are ____ that specify what someone will know, care about, or be able to do as a result of a learning experience.",
        answer: "goals",
        options: [
            "goals",
            "purposes",
            "targets",
            "plans"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 45,
        question: "What are three main categories or “domains” of the learning skills?",
        answer: "Cognitive domain, Affective domain, Psychomotor domain",
        options: [
            "Cognitive domain, Affective domain, Reflective domain",
            "Cognitive domain, Affective domain, Proactive domain",
            "Cognitive domain, Affective domain, Psychomotor domain",
            "Cognitive domain, Reflective domain, Psychomotor domain"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 46,
        question: "The “Psychomotor Domain” of learning skills means",
        answer: "What you should be able to do",
        options: [
            "What you should know",
            "What you should care about",
            "What you should be able to do",
            "None of these is correct"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 47,
        question: "Which of the following domains of learning skills means “What you should care about”?",
        answer: "Affective domain",
        options: [
            "Cognitive domain",
            "Affective domain",
            "Psychomotor domain",
            "Reflective domain"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 48,
        question: "All of the followings are the ways to use critical thinking to evaluate information, EXCEPT",
        answer: "None",
        options: [
            "Being receptive to having your opinions changed",
            "Having an inquiring mind",
            "Accepting something without asking for evidence",
            "Questioning your own conclusions"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 49,
        question: "Which is the highest learning-skill level of Bloom’s Taxonomy?",
        answer: "Create",
        options: [
            "Analyze",
            "Apply",
            "Evaluate",
            "Create"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 50,
        question: "Which is the lowest learning-skill level of Bloom’s Taxonomy?",
        answer: "Remember",
        options: [
            "Remember",
            "Understand",
            "Analyze",
            "Apply"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 51,
        question: "_____ is “the ability to judge, check, and even critique the value of material for a given purpose”.",
        answer: "Evaluating",
        options: [
            "Applying",
            "Evaluating",
            "Analyzing",
            "Creating"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 52,
        question: "_____ is “the ability to grasp or construct meaning from oral, written, and graphic messages”.",
        answer: "Understanding",
        options: [
            "Remembering",
            "Understanding",
            "Analyzing",
            "Applying"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 53,
        question: "The “Applying” skill of Bloom’s Taxonomy is: ",
        answer: "Ability to use learned material (or implement the material) in new and concrete situations",
        options: [
            "Ability to recognize or recall gained knowledge",
            "Ability to use learned material (or implement the material) in new and concrete situations",
            "Ability to judge, check, and even critique the value of material for a given purpose",
            "Ability to grasp or construct meaning from oral, written, and graphic messages"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 54,
        question: "Thought and thinking can be understood as _____within the mind.",
        answer: "Patterns - Systems and Schemes",
        options: [
            "Patterns - Systems and Schemes",
            "Order and Structure",
            "Act and Control",
            "Analyze and Evaluate"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 55,
        question: "Creative thinking is",
        answer: "All of these are correct",
        options: [
            "a way of employing strategies to clear your mind so that your thoughts and ideas can transcend what appear to be the limitations of a problem",
            "important because it helps you look at problems and situations from a fresh perspective",
            "a way to develop novel or unorthodox solutions that do not depend wholly on past or current solutions",
            "All of these are correct"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 56,
        question: "Which statement is NOT true about creativity?",
        answer: "Human is not innately creative",
        options: [
            "All humans are innately creative, especially if creativity is understood as a problem-solving skill",
            "As a creative thinker, you are curious, optimistic, and imaginative",
            "Creativity is inspired when there is a problem to solve",
            "Human is not innately creative"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 57,
        question: "Which of the following statements is NOT correct about a creative thinker?",
        answer: "See problems as limits of development",
        options: [
            "Be curious, optimistic",
            "See problems as limits of development",
            "Always challenge assumptions and suspend judgment",
            "Be imaginative"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 58,
        question: "College is great ground for enhancing creative thinking skills as in the below examples, EXCEPT",
        answer: "Create plan for better communication with your colleagues",
        options: [
            "Design sample exam questions to test your knowledge as you study for a final",
            "Devise a social media strategy for a club on campus",
            "Create plan for better communication with your colleagues",
            "Propose an education plan for a major you are designing for yourself"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 59,
        question: "Strategies to stimulate your creative thinking include",
        answer: "All of these are correct",
        options: [
            "Sleep on it",
            "Put yourself in nerve-racking situations once in a while to fire up your brain.",
            "Keep a notebook with you so you always have a way to record fleeting thoughts.",
            "All of these are correct"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 60,
        question: "Key strategy (ies) for success in evaluating information",
        answer: "All of these are correct",
        options: [
            "Examine arguments",
            "Clarify thinking",
            "Cultivate “habits of mind”",
            "All of these are correct"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 61,
        question: "Among the tips for creative thinking, What does “Sensing” mean?",
        answer: "Be a good observer of people, nature, and events around you",
        options: [
            "Be a good observer of people, nature, and events around you",
            "Be empathetic with other people",
            "Have more fun learning",
            "Be open to insight as ideas pop into your mind"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 62,
        question: "How to develop your creative thinking skill through “Drawing”?",
        answer: "Use mind-mapping to capture ideas",
        options: [
            "Develop ideas and expand their possibilities",
            "Use mind-mapping to capture ideas",
            "Explain how your ideas move beyond the status quo and contribute to a discussion",
            "Take notes"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 63,
        question: "Which action does belong to the strategy “Identify available solutions”?",
        answer: "Compare and contrast possible solutions",
        options: [
            "Identify the problem",
            "Organize the information logically",
            "Compare and contrast possible solutions",
            "Defend your solution"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 64,
        question: "Which is a fact about Creative Thinking?",
        answer: "Only few problems require complex technological solutions",
        options: [
            "Every problem has only one solution or one right answer",
            "Ideas either come or they don’t. Nothing will help – certainly not structure",
            "The best answer or solution or method has already been discovered",
            "Only few problems require complex technological solutions"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 65,
        question: "Which is NOT a fiction about Creative Thinking?",
        answer: "Creative solution should be answer for all problems",
        options: [
            "Every problem has only one solution or one right answer",
            "The best answer or solution or method has already been discovered",
            "Creative answers are technologically complex",
            "Creative solution should be answer for all problems"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 66,
        question: "Which technology can help students establish a sense of community with their class and engage in ongoing threaded conversations on assigned readings and topics highlighting diverse points of view?",
        answer: "Discussion boards",
        options: [
            "Interactive whiteboards",
            "Discussion boards",
            "Student-response systems",
            "Digital camcorders"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 67,
        question: "In which way does “Wikis” contribute to our ability to be critical and creative thinkers?",
        answer: "All of these are correct",
        options: [
            "Wikis can help students coordinate, compile, synthesize, and present individual or group projects or research.",
            "Wikis can help students build and share group resources and knowledge.",
            "Wikis can help students provide peer review, feedback, and critiques.",
            "All of these are correct"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 68,
        question: "What is Critical thinking?",
        answer: "Is clear, reasonable, reflective thinking focused on deciding what to believe or do",
        options: [
            "Is clear, reasonable, reflective thinking focused on deciding what to believe or do",
            "Is a way of thinking to criticize what other people say",
            "Is reflective thinking focused on claiming and proving other people your ideas or opinions",
            "Is simple thinking that memorizing facts or blindly accepting what you hear or read"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 69,
        question: "What are the characteristics of Critical thinking?",
        answer: "All of these are correct",
        options: [
            "Examining assumptions",
            "Challenging reasoning",
            "Uncovering biases",
            "All of these are correct"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 70,
        question: "Which is NOT a characteristic of Critical thinking?",
        answer: "Group thinking",
        options: [
            "Skepticism",
            "Group thinking",
            "Examining assumptions",
            "Uncovering biases"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 71,
        question: "What is the meaning of the word “Logic” in the Ancient Greek logike?",
        answer: "The science or art of reasoning",
        options: [
            "A process of questioning information and data",
            "It means asking probing questions",
            "The science or art of reasoning",
            "It refers to using knowledge, facts, and data to solve problems"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 72,
        question: "Which of the following statements is NOT correct?",
        answer: "“Logic” cannot help to distinguish between good and bad reasoning",
        options: [
            "The word “Logic” comes from the Ancient Greek logike",
            "“Logic” refers to the science or art of reasoning",
            "“Logic” allows a person to evaluate arguments and reasoning",
            "“Logic” cannot help to distinguish between good and bad reasoning"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 73,
        question: "What is the purpose of the critical thinker when asking “What is happening?”?",
        answer: "To gather the basic information and begin to think of questions",
        options: [
            "To gather the basic information and begin to think of questions",
            "To see where the information come from and how it was constructed",
            "To check if any information is missing",
            "To know if other ideas or possibilities exist"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 74,
        question: "What is the similarity of Critical thinking and Problem-solving?",
        answer: "They both refer to using knowledge, facts, and data to solve problems effectively",
        options: [
            "They both focus on identifying, selecting, defending solution",
            "They both refer to using knowledge, facts, and data to solve problems effectively",
            "They are efficient and rewarding process",
            "They are fundamentally process of questioning information and data"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 75,
        question: "In order to “Define the problem”, which actions should we take?",
        answer: "Identify the problem, Provide as many supporting details as possible, Provide examples, Organize the information logically",
        options: [
            "Identify the problem, Identify facts, Provide examples, Organize the information logically",
            "Identify the problem, Identify facts, Identify your most important goals",
            "Identify the problem, Provide as many supporting details as possible, Provide examples, Organize the information logically",
            "Identify the problem, Provide as many supporting details as possible, Identify your most important goals, Gather information and facts"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 76,
        question: "Which is TRUE about long-term orientation culture",
        answer: "Long-term orientation is often marked by persistence, thrift and frugality",
        options: [
            "United States has a more long-term approach to life and results",
            "If  you  work  within  a  culture  that  has  a long-term  orientation,  you  may  need  to  place  greater  emphasis  on reciprocation of greetings, gifts, and rewards.",
            "Long-term orientation is often marked by persistence, thrift and frugality",
            "All of these"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 77,
        question: "Which is TRUE about short-term orientation culture",
        answer: "If  you  work  within  a  culture  that  has  a  short-term  orientation,  you  may  need  to  place  greater  emphasis  on reciprocation of greetings, gifts, and rewards",
        options: [
            "Many countries in Asia value a short-term orientation",
            "If  you  work  within  a  culture  that  has  a  short-term  orientation,  you  may  need  to  place  greater  emphasis  on reciprocation of greetings, gifts, and rewards",
            "Short-term orientation is often marked by persistence, thrift and frugality, and an order to relationships based on age and status",
            "All of these"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 78,
        question: "“_______enables one individual or group to make the decisions that affect others, and to enforce control”",
        answer: "Power-over",
        options: [
            "Power-from-within",
            "Power-with",
            "Power-over",
            "Power-from-outside"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 79,
        question: "Which type of power can manifest itself when we stand, walk, and speak.",
        answer: "Power-from-within",
        options: [
            "Power-from-within",
            "Power-with",
            "Power-over",
            "None of these answers"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 80,
        question: "“Arises from our sense of connection, our bonding with other human beings, and with the environment” can be used to describe which type of power.",
        answer: "Power-with",
        options: [
            "Power-from-within",
            "Power-with",
            "Power-over",
            "None of these answers"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 81,
        question: "“The power of a strong individual in a group of equals, the power not to command, but to suggest and be listened to, to begin something and see it happen”  can be used to describe which type of power.",
        answer: "Power-with",
        options: [
            "Power-from-within",
            "Power-with",
            "Power-over",
            "None of these answers"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 82,
        question: "Which of the following idioms can be used to describe the relationship between power and oppression.",
        answer: "Two sides of the same coin",
        options: [
            "A blessing in disguise	",
            "The best of both worlds",
            "Get out of hand",
            "Two sides of the same coin"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 83,
        question: "When does a person obtain the expert power?",
        answer: "Person A has more expertise knowledge than person B",
        options: [
            "Person A has higher status than person B",
            "Person A has more expertise knowledge than person B",
            "Person A group is bigger than person B",
            "Person A has more friend than person B"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 84,
        question: "What are the possible behavior responses in the consequences of power?",
        answer: "Commitment and compliance",
        options: [
            "Trustworthiness and betrayal",
            "Complaint and compliance",
            "Commitment and compliance",
            "Trustworthiness and resistance"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 85,
        question: "Why being socially connected is an important way of dealing with stress?",
        answer: "Because it’s easy to isolate yourself when you feel stressed",
        options: [
            "Because it’s easy to isolate yourself when you feel stressed",
            "Because it helps you to maintain a normal routine",
            "Because other people can give you good advices about your problems",
            "Because it can help distract you from your problems for a while"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 86,
        question: "When subordinates are under conditions of coercive power, which following behavior responses are likely to be used?",
        answer: "Resistance",
        options: [
            "Tolerance",
            "Enthusiasm",
            "Acceptance",
            "Resistance"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 87,
        question: "According to the research on diversity, what makes diverse groups/teams are better at decision-making and problem-solving?",
        answer: "Tend to focus more on facts",
        options: [
            "Tend to focus more on facts",
            "Less additional idea",
            "More variety of personality",
            "Has different belief"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 88,
        question: "What is the final best practice for boosting multicultural skills?",
        answer: "Developing cognitive complexity",
        options: [
            "Developing cultural intelligence",
            "Developing cognitive complexity",
            "Developing cultural competence",
            "Developing cross-cultural skills"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 89,
        question: "The common story that can be used to reflect individualistic cultures is?",
        answer: "Superman",
        options: [
            "Tom and Jerry",
            "Spider-man",
            "Superman",
            "Mickey mouse"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 90,
        question: "Which of the following countries represent individualistic cultures?",
        answer: "The United States",
        options: [
            "Japan",
            "Cuba",
            "Vietnam",
            "The United States"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 91,
        question: "Which of the following can be seen as positive sides of conflict?",
        answer: "Help individuals and group members grow and develop self-identities",
        options: [
            "Help individuals and group members grow and develop self-identities",
            "Affect the social climate of the group and inhibit group cohesiveness",
            "Making people divert energies away from the performance",
            "Influence on stress and the psychophysical consequences of stress"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 92,
        question: "Which conflict-handling mode can be used when opponents with equal power are committed to mutually exclusive goals ",
        answer: "Compromising ",
        options: [
            "Avoiding ",
            "Competing",
            "Compromising ",
            "Accommodating "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 93,
        question: "Which of the following are the five modes for conflict resolution developed by Kenneth Thomas (1976)?",
        answer: "(1) competing, (2) combination, (3) compromising,  (4) avoiding, and (5) accommodating",
        options: [
            "(1) competing, (2) collaborating, (3) compromising, (4) avoiding, and (5) accommodating",
            "(1) competing, (2) combination, (3) aggravating,  (4) resistance, and (5) ignore",
            "(1) competing, (2) combination, (3) compromising,  (4) avoiding, and (5) accommodating",
            "(1) competing, (2) collaborating, (3) aggravating, (4) resistance, and (5) ignore"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 94,
        question: "What is the quickest and easiest solution to reduce conflict?",
        answer: "Physical separation",
        options: [
            "Physical separation",
            "Use of rules and regulations",
            "Third-party consultation",
            "Confrontation and negotiation"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 95,
        question: "In the Leader Trait Research which trait includes strong analytical abilities?",
        answer: "Cognitive ability",
        options: [
            "Self-confidence",
            "Leadership motivation",
            "Drive",
            "Cognitive ability"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 96,
        question: "Which conflict-handling mode can be used when an issue is trivial, or when more important issues are pressing ",
        answer: "Avoiding ",
        options: [
            "Avoiding ",
            "Competing",
            "Compromising ",
            "Accommodating "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 97,
        question: "Which conflict-handling mode can be used when issues are more important to others than yourself—to satisfy others and maintain cooperation",
        answer: "Accommodating ",
        options: [
            "Avoiding ",
            "Competing",
            "Compromising ",
            "Accommodating "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 98,
        question: "Status can be defined as:",
        answer: "A person’s perceived level of importance or significance within aparticular context.",
        options: [
            "A person’s perceived level of importance or significance within a particular context.",
            "A result of power, with its roots in global colonialism and conquests",
            "An action can deny certain groups jobs that pay living wages, can establish unequal. can deny affordable housing, and the list goes on",
            "None of these above"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 99,
        question: "Which power of the following exists when person B submits to person A because B feels that A has a right to exert power in a certain domain?",
        answer: "Legitimate Power",
        options: [
            "Expert Power",
            "Legitimate Power",
            "Reward Power",
            "Coercive Power"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 100,
        question: "Authority is another name of:",
        answer: "Coercive Power",
        options: [
            "Expert Power",
            "Legitimate Power",
            "Reward Power",
            "Coercive Power"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 101,
        question: "Coercive power is also referred to as:",
        answer: "Punish power",
        options: [
            "Respect power",
            "Team power",
            "Discipline power",
            "Punish power"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 102,
        question: "What is an example of  Expert Power?",
        answer: "Professors presumably have power in the classroom because of their mastery of a particular subject matter.",
        options: [
            "Professors presumably have power in the classroom because of their mastery of a particular subject matter.",
            "A supervisor has a right to assign work.",
            "Salary and promotion among most blue-collar workers is based on a labor contract, not a performance appraisal.",
            "In many organizations, supervisors and managers really do not control very many rewards."
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 103,
        question: "Reward Power exists when:",
        answer: "when person A has power over person B because A controls rewards that B wants.",
        options: [
            "person A has power over person B because A can administer some form of punishment to B.",
            "person A gains power because A has knowledge or expertise relevant to B. ",
            "when person B submits to person A because B feels that A has a right to exert power in a certain domain",
            "when person A has power over person B because A controls rewards that B wants."
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 104,
        question: "Last stage in the model of the Conflict Process ",
        answer: "Outcome",
        options: [
            "Frustration ",
            "Conceptualization ",
            "Behavior ",
            "Outcome"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 105,
        question: "Of all the bases of power available to man, the power to hurt others is possibly the most often used, most often condemned and most difficult to control.",
        answer: "Coercive power",
        options: [
            "Reward Power",
            "Coercive power",
            "Referent Power",
            "Legitimate Power"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 106,
        question: "Which of the four key cultural differences could be considered offensive by some?",
        answer: "Direct versus indirect communication",
        options: [
            "Direct versus indirect communication",
            "Accents and fluency",
            "Differing attitudes toward hierarchy",
            "Conflicting decision-making norms"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 107,
        question: "When one language is dominated in the group, what could happen to the person who can't speak it?",
        answer: "All the above",
        options: [
            "Less competent in a group",
            "Feel left out",
            "Be seen as contributing less",
            "All the above"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 108,
        question: "Which of the following provides a great advantage to the leader in their relationships with teammates?",
        answer: "Cultural intelligence",
        options: [
            "Authority to control teammates",
            "Superior status",
            "Cultural intelligence",
            "Explicit in communication"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 109,
        question: "Which of the following intervention technique should be used sparingly?",
        answer: "Managerial",
        options: [
            "Adaptation",
            "Structural",
            "Managerial",
            "Voluntary or involuntary removal "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 110,
        question: "When conflicts arise, what intervention technique should be used as a last resort?",
        answer: "Voluntary or involuntary removal ",
        options: [
            "Adaptation",
            "Structural",
            "Managerial",
            "Voluntary or involuntary removal "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 111,
        question: "Which traits are taking on increasing importance in the business world today?",
        answer: "Multiculturalism and cultural intelligence",
        options: [
            "Multiculturalism and cultural intelligence",
            "Verbal and nonverbal communication",
            "Cultural intelligence and language",
            "Style, pace, language and nonverbal communication"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 112,
        question: "When do the Conflicts of misperceived differences arise?",
        answer: "Interpret each other’s actions or emotions erroneously",
        options: [
            "Reinforcing or weakening each other’s impact",
            "Interpret each other’s actions or emotions erroneously",
            "Differ over how to reach goals or pursue values",
            "Hold totally different values or rank the same values in a significantly different order"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 113,
        question: "What makes Relationship conflicts become hard to cope with?",
        answer: "People frequently aren’t admitted for what they are",
        options: [
            "Intimidate personal ego",
            "Increased sense of self-worth",
            "Misconception",
            "People frequently aren’t admitted for what they are"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 114,
        question: "Which behavior people often DON’T display when they are being deceptive",
        answer: "Increased smiling",
        options: [
            "Reduction in eye contact while engaged in a conversation",
            "Awkward pauses in conversation",
            "Decreased rate of speech",
            "Increased smiling"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 115,
        question: "The word “power” literally means:",
        answer: "“To be able to”",
        options: [
            "“To be able to”",
            "“The influence”",
            "“The strength”",
            "None of these answers"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 116,
        question: "Pay raises, promotions, desirable job assignments, more responsibility, new equipment are example of:",
        answer: "Reward power",
        options: [
            "Reward power",
            "Legitimate",
            "Expert Power",
            "Coercive Power "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 117,
        question: "To use THIS power: Punish in private , Inform subordinates of rules and penalties or this power can be used without jeopardizing personal integrity",
        answer: "Coercive power ",
        options: [
            "Reward power ",
            "Legitimate power ",
            "Evaluation criteria",
            "Coercive power "
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 118,
        question: "____cultures focus on the needs of the nation, community, family, or group of workers",
        answer: "Collectivist ",
        options: [
            "Collectivist ",
            "Individualistic",
            "Low-Power Distance",
            "High-Power Distance"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 119,
        question: "These conflicts, which relate to questions about what choices to make in a given situation, rest on differing views of the facts",
        answer: "conflicts of substance",
        options: [
            "conflicts of substance",
            "Conflicts of process",
            "Conflicts of misperceived differences",
            "None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 120,
        question: "First stage in the model of the Conflict Process ",
        answer: "Frustration ",
        options: [
            "Frustration ",
            "Conceptualization ",
            "Behavior ",
            "Outcome"
        ]
    }
    //a
];